<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Donors on SJTU Irving T. Ho Scholarships</title>
    <link>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Donors on SJTU Irving T. Ho Scholarships</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>珍珠生捐助人</title>
      <link>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/pearldonors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/pearldonors/</guid>
      <description>   姓名 毕业院校 当前所在国家/城市     王荣腾 国立台湾大学 美国   徐 强 香港中文大学 香港   温晓青 清华大学 日本   柳春生 清华大学 美国   陈星浩 清华大学 美国   宋培林 清华大学 美国   黄 宇 清华大学 深圳   石 峰 清华大学 美国   魏 海 清华大学 北京   南 昊 清华大学 美国   许舸夫 东南大学 美国   何之行 国立台湾大学 台北   郭彦伶 国立台湾大学 美国   赵冠琳 国立台湾大学 美国   许承郁 国立台湾大学 美国   王启照 国立清华大学 美国   王 瑾 上海交通大学 美国   王 辉 上海交通大学 美国   方 舟 上海交通大学 美国   沈承杳 上海交通大学 美国   李金波 上海交通大学 美国   王培俊 上海交通大学 上海   邹理豪 上海交通大学 美国   胡翰彬 上海交通大学 美国   邓舒文 上海交通大学 美国   杜家全 上海交通大学研究所 上海    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>第二期捐赠者</title>
      <link>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/donors2nd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/donors2nd/</guid>
      <description>Name Affiliation Location     Alfred Xu (徐辉) Irving T. Ho Fellow &amp;lsquo;07;&amp;lsquo;08 Shanghai, China   Chengyao Shen (沈程杳) Irving T. Ho Fellow &amp;lsquo;09 Singapore   Dr. L.-T. Wang (王荣腾) SynTest Technologies California, USA   Ms. Susan Chang (張華茹) SynTest Technologies California, USA   Gavin Du (杜家全) SJTU Alum; Air Products and Chemicals Shanghai, China   Ms. Fangfang Li (黎芳芳) SJTU Alum; SynTest Technologies Shanghai, China   Xiangfeng Li (李向丰) SJTU Alum; NVIDIA Shanghai, China   Ben Liu (刘峰) SJTU Alum; AMD Shanghai, China   Alice Yu (游中靜) University of California, San Diego (UCSD) California, USA   Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>第三期捐赠者</title>
      <link>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/donors3rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjtu-irving-t-ho-scholarship.github.io/donors/donors3rd/</guid>
      <description> 捐款发起人(11名)    姓名 备注     王荣腾 华腾科技创办人兼何宜慈基金会董事长   王瑾 2007届本科校友，2004年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   徐辉 2009届本科校友，2007及2008年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   王辉 2009届本科校友，2007及2008年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   李金波 2010届本科校友，2007年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   沈程杳 2010届本科校友，2009年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   应碧丞 2013届本科校友，2011年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   胡翰彬 2013届本科校友，2011年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   吴文颢 2013届本科校友，2012年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   杜家全 2013届硕士校友，何宜慈基金会名誉院士   邓舒文 2016届本科校友，2014年奖学金获得者    上海交通大学何宜慈奖学金获得者(11名)    姓名 备注     高阳 2007届本科校友，2004年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   范鸿敏 本科校友，2004年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   曾令全 2008届本科校友，2004年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   江韵 2009届本科校友，2005年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   赵一振 2010届本科校友，2006年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   杜杰琼 2011届本科校友，2009年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   邹理豪 2014届本科校友，2012年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   杜广祥 2014届本科校友，2012年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   杨添易 2014届本科校友，2013年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   王璞申 2015届本科校友，2013年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   刘康奇 2016届本科校友，2014年交大何宜慈奖学金获得者   邓舒文 2016届本科校友，2014年奖学金获得者    上海交通大学校友及前教职员工(26名)    姓名 备注     Shu Cai 本科校友   Xinwei Chen 2010届本科校友   陈栋 2007届本科校友   陈志翔 2007届本科校友   范原博 2010届本科校友   郭辰曦 2010届本科校友   李铭 2007届本科校友   吕超 2010届本科校友   钱智量 前教职员工   宋阳 2010届本科校友   孙守安 2007届本科校友   唐伊纳 2011届本科校友   田欣波 本科校友   屠敏敏 2003届本科校友   项晶 2007届本科校友   谢金融 2007届本科校友   余容 2007届本科校友   朱晶阳 2013届本科校友   赵力航 2007届本科校友   张乐林 2007届本科校友   朱彦 2010届本科校友   郑永鹤 本科校友   周金佳 2007届本科校友   周彦祺 2011届本科校友   匿名 1991届本科校友   匿名 2007届本科校友    何宜慈基金会爱心人士(3名)    姓名 备注     何邦仪 何宜慈博士长子   南昊 清华大学校友，2009年清华大学何宜慈奖学金获得者   许承郁 台湾大学校友，2011年台湾大学何宜慈奖学金获得者    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>